<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>E-Learning on Bogdan V. Hotea</title>
    <link>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/tags/e-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in E-Learning on Bogdan V. Hotea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.144.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:04:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/tags/e-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Provide Compliant Feedback to Interview Candidates</title>
      <link>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/interview-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:04:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/interview-candidates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This interactive training module demo guides managers through structured interview techniques, with a focus on reducing unconscious bias. In this demo, users step into the role of a hiring manager navigating real-world scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The full module was originally designed as a branching storyline featuring quizzes, drag-and-drop exercises, and decision-making challenges. As users progress, they collect medal pieces — a playful reward system that unlocks the final quiz once completed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlights-include&#34;&gt;Highlights include:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scenario-based learning with meaningful choices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clean, cartoon-style visuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decluttered interface with key info residing in pop-ups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accessible layout with keyboard-friendly navigation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collectable badges as a reward for completed challenges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custom buttons, icons and visuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-the-module&#34;&gt;Try the Module&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/files/interview-candidates/story.html&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;600&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;iframe&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;➡️ Use this link to &lt;a href=&#34;https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/files/interview-candidates/story.html&#34;&gt;preview the e-learning module&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s an Embargo?</title>
      <link>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/embargo-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:03:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/embargo-training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This short demo of a compliance module introduces embargoes and economic sanctions in plain language. It helps employees understand how these restrictions affect day-to-day operations and decision-making. The training includes interactive scenarios and quiz questions that break complex topics into manageable, digestible parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although the subject matter is nuanced, I focused on distilling each concept to its essence — keeping the slides clean, simple, and focused. Learners receive instant feedback after each question, along with a summary of correct and incorrect responses. This helps reinforce understanding while allowing learners to reflect and adjust as they go.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Produce Green Code</title>
      <link>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/green-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/green-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This short demo showcases a selection of slides exploring eco-friendly coding practices. It’s designed to raise awareness among developers and product teams about their environmental footprint — using real-world examples, animated graphics, and accessible design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In response to stakeholder feedback, I focused on simplifying complex ideas into clear, digestible chunks. The visual approach draws from familiar green and eco-focused aesthetics to strengthen message clarity and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;highlights-include&#34;&gt;Highlights include:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactivity such as carousels and Multiple choice questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Infographics used to break down complex topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smooth transitions between sections&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unique visual identity that embodies the concept of &amp;ldquo;eco-friendliness&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custom buttons and visuals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-the-module&#34;&gt;Try the Module&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/files/green-code/story.html&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;600&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;iframe&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;➡️ Use this link to &lt;a href=&#34;https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/files/green-code/story.html&#34;&gt;preview the e-learning module&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Guest Complaints</title>
      <link>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/guest-complaints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdanvasilehotea.github.io/posts/guest-complaints/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This interactive demo was designed for front-of-house (FOH) staff at a hospitality chain, focusing on handling guest complaints according to company standards. It uses a gamified approach, presenting users with three distinct scenarios they can freely explore from a central menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In each scenario, users are asked to respond to a guest complaint. A correct answer earns them a star badge, and collecting all three badges unlocks the training’s conclusion. Because the scenarios can be accessed in any order, the progress bar updates dynamically to reflect real-time advancement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
